It is said that a man has hung himself in the barn, in one of the beams.
Who this man is you try to find out.
Those who live here experience a huge discomfort when trying to stay in the barn.
And what is in there wants you to leave quickly.
The family reports that you see figures inside and outside the houses, who look at them.
And the feeling inside the dilapidated house is that it is a child.
A boy and a girl.
Outside the house, there is a man standing at the house knot and observes them.
The boy in the family who has his room on the ground floor closest to the kitchen talks to someone they can't see.
On this land previously stood an old Norrbotten farm, which unfortunately burned down.
And the flames brought a woman and her child who never got out.
Perhaps it is these unsavory spirits that still haunt the houses.
Then we have entered here in Piteå, to this agricultural property.
Actually, there are three properties, it is this one since the a little more down and then we also have the barn.
So much to investigate.
It is specific stuff that happens, we should focus on them.
We will look if we can make these phenomena happen, but we do not know that.
It can happen now, it can happen when.
But we have had small things that have happened before we started here.
I think we have even captured a shadow, on surveillance.
And it all made us jump to.
It was very interesting to see it.
In fact, we have not been documented before, not this way.
We have seen it before, at the safari investigation, but then it did not record it.
But now we were on the recording that was lucky.
This sequence shows what it looks like when the camera goes to Nightvision as we usually see.
So it was very, very special.
Clearly.
And I think like this, now it's pretty much to investigate, many rooms.
Then there are specific phenomena they say hands here, so I think we should try to go on the hot spot we have.
Should we start in the kitchen?
I think we should start in the kitchen, but we should also focus on a special room.
Where a little guy gets things to him, he talks to something before he goes to bed.
Exactly and it's just straight through this door.
It must be awful as a parent to lie down and hear him talk about everything possible in there.
In the kitchen where we are now, we have a surveillance camera too, behind me.
And here we have this box, above all, pulled out and these knives change position.
And ends up in another cabinet.
It is absolutely incredible.
If we can catch it, it is absolutely wonderful.
The Holy Graile of everything.
But as I said we have lots of instruments, all equipment is here so we can always go and get more.
It's not huge.
We will pick up some instruments, we have to put on jackets, it is cold out there and cold put inside the other house.
Plus in the barn.
But right now we are in the heat.
We go in here, I wonder if we should have a tool going.
If you start it there and immediately open the door, we will see what is said.
I also think the PDA, Paranormal Direct Answer.
It works in case something comes to the right or to the left, so it glows red or green.
Just.
We prepare the whole room and we will see what happens.
Shit what scared I was.
What then?
If you do it, go to this blue vibrant light that is in front of us on the bed.
Is it the little girl who usually says things to him who is here?
I can say, we have surveillance now in most buildings, if something happens, Lennie will shout to us right away.
He sits on the bus watching the surveillance.
If we get some name, he will look if he can relate the name to this farm.
So maybe we get a better understanding of what it is or who it is.
We must not forget, there was a Norrbotten farm that was about where the barn is and it burned down.
It is said that a woman and two children burned inside.
Just.
And that is what we are thinking about if this girl has entered this building, which is also affecting this boy.
We have to test everything here now.
We don't have the faintest about what we are dealing with here.
It can also be something very negative that has come in here.
These shivers that come, they are interesting.
It comes as in waves.
Love.
Here is nothing now.
It felt here, right here.
Can we have a name?
Are there initials?
It's hard to say in and of itself ...
We have other things happening here.
We have a drapery down in the basement of the shower, where they hear this little girl laughing and turning on the drapery.
We will test that theory and be one on the inside of the drapery and so some are outside and then we will see if the little girl can come in there.
It will be a damn humming though down there, because it has a ... what is it called?
Dehumidifier.
And we can't turn them off, they don't want it.
I'll try to get down on my knees here and see if we get something, if it is the little girl who is here.
My name is Tony, this is Niclas and Johan is the one who is filming here.
Are you below?
Where!
It is a static field.
Are you under the bed now?
I felt your hand or something.
Damn!
I test a spirit box and see if we get through her voice.
It was as if something caressed my fingers here.
What did it say?
Time.
Did you hear this just?
Here.
It sounded like .. yes it may have it.
"Go up"
It sounded like going up.
Or up.
"Leave"
Turn it off.
This man, he is seen inside the house, but he is also outside and just looks at them.
He wears a swallow hat.
Just.
And a rock.
And boots.
So he just stands still.
They even screamed at him, what do you want?!
And then he just goes away.
That was sick, it was a great feeling that.
It is cool, while you get the touch, you get a static field that pops up there.
It was like I went into it, but it continued to wander along my fingers.
You get to play with this teddy bear or with that coffee pot there.
Throw them down if you want.
Say your name, you who make it smell so good.
"People live here"
This is also interesting, I mean we have these phenomena that happen and right now it feels like we are talking to quite a few around here.
But I do not know, what we are trying to focus on when we are here is what he experiences.
Is it really a little girl or is it something else that has been generated from something completely different?
And we focus a lot on these phenomena, because it's the ones that stand out.
It is the rocking horse, the bedroom there, the shower down there and we have one to bedroom up there where a wardrobe door is usually opened.
And there are also moved there.
It is caps that end up in completely different places.
I try Ovilus here and we'll see.
Someone here?
Angry I just got up ..
Are you angry because we're here?
Don't like us?
Can you get this rocking horse to swing once for us?
You've got it to swing several times before.
When the family has been sitting here.
I try to listen while talking, on the whole house.
We hear drops, something that beats out here, you hear a lot.
But it is recurring, it is the same all the time.
So it's nothing paranormal.
No.
Can you move on a cap hanging here on the wall?
EVP is recorded.
"Kannor"
It's not the same discomfort here either.
It's his room down there, so far, right?
If you want to go on the instruments and what we know, it is down there.
But then if it moves throughout the house, the camera takes it, if these phenomena happens.
But right in there it seems that it is centered.
I have a theory of the little energy that is there, using him an incredible amount.
He probably has a lot of energy.
So that's why it is in that room.
That he becomes like the battery to it.
Do you see the teapot I put to you?
That noise, I put this one.
Can you say what your name is for us?
Look look!
Good!
Go near it.
It glows on both.
Sit next to it and talk.
So maybe we will hear your voice.
Like it went.
Yes, like it didn't really cope, did you see?
It went away.
Strange, I don't usually get anything, but in my head all the time, it's a maiden name.
Which has been holding on for probably ten minutes.
Now I have to say, Lisa, Lisa, Lisa ...
But we will also look at where he has been seen.
Around here, so we'll see if we can get any mapping.
The instruments are still underway here.
Lennie has full control over it, so he shouts, Johan you have Walkie Talkie, so we will hear it.
We run both SLS camera and heat camera at the same time.
And it is in this house where they see people stand here.
Anyone here?
It is interesting, a candlestick is up and running.
Should I extinguish it?
Do it.
Do we have someone in here?
Which usually stands at these windows and look out.
He has been seen standing here.
And look straight at the person when they come in.
If you stand there Niclas, I'll see if I get an upset.
See if we can get him with you.
I want these kids here ...
Now it's back!
Stuck on the other side ...
Yes, there!
Behind your back now.
But that doesn't look like a child, it looks like something is climbing on your back now.
Climb up!
Take off my cap, turn off my cap, pull in my jacket.
"Naughty"
Naughty.
Cool, there will be a cold up after the back.
Yes, it wanders up longer and farther after down back.
Hands touch your hand there.
It moves your hand where Niclas.
It stood up, it squatted huh?
Yes, it squatted, now it stands up.
It was a child.
Hi, we hear you.
Are you called Lisa?
One more, though it is there now, on that side.
It stands up on the bench.
It also looks like a small child.
There are two kids here.
Are the kids here now, you who passed away here?
Do you see Johan?
Yes, I have full control.
One sitting on the floor, one standing on the bench behind you Niclas.
"Mom comes"
Mom is coming.
"Stand there!"
Bert was someone who said.
Is it the man who took his life in the barn?
Is it you that people usually see outside?
I would like to test a thing Tony.
I close this ..
I would like to test stand where that barn burned down.
On the ground out there.
See if there is something that pops up next to me there.
Should we test it before we go into the barn?
But it is interesting, we have two energies moving here.
They come through pretty well.
But there are still too many questions.
But it's like, there are two children and the legends are there.
It's not far, we can only go there before we go into the barn.
Lets go out.
So if it is you, who passed away out there, follow us.
As you can see, we are just off the bus, what you hear now is our heater to the bus.
But we have a good bit more ...
Damn was anyone standing there?
Care for the Chinese.
Someone stood on the balcony there.
On the balcony?
Would you be able to show yourself to us once?
A little time.
No mapping on SLS camera here.
I'll try once under the bed here.
Nothing.
We wait for Johan while he takes off his jacket before we continue, then this happens.
Damn, now he was there I think.
He was damn behind the car.
Huh?
Yes, hell!
What you see a lot of Niclas.
Damn I also want to see this fucking old man.
But that's because I look around, I look out all the time.
Now there was a black shape behind the car.
While we are fixing and taking off jackets, I look out at the same place, but now he stands behind the car.
Those who live here have two cars and they left one left.
And now he was behind the car.
Unfortunately, we have no surveillance out here, but I am who see it.
Now that Johan is taking off the jacket for us to be back.
It's pretty interesting, I don't know why he turns out to me.
It's as you said, you want to see too and I understand that.
But I am one as a person who looks all the time, I may seem nonchalant, but I work with everything.
I let the body feel, but here I just turn my head, I see him stand there ...
Same dark figure, straight out here.
So I think it's awesome, he goes around here, but he doesn't come in here it seems.
But what we have focused on all evening is more this with the child
Because it is one that has a slightly more aggressive tone as well.
You also have to think that it is their land and we try to get a little more right to those who live here.
What it is that can affect him.
Because they also give him pretty negative thoughts.
So it is very difficult for us, I can't put my finger on why that energy does.
But we will test a little more, I think, we will put out a pyramid that we have.
The Pyramid of Truth.
I will put it inside and we will not be in the room.
We will stand here somewhere.
And this one will then push out rays on each side.
Who senses if something breaks this, then it will indicate with green or red.
And then it comes pipe and has its own life in there.
Then I wait out here.
As you can see, it turns green and red.
Two beeps.
So it will be on the bed here now, about this girl or whatever it is.
So Johan will direct the camera between us here now.
Now we have placed this one and it detects if there is any movement next to it.
I put this one, where we had the static field.
Now it is under the bed.
You can play with it if you want.
It was Tony again that passed, so you see how sensitive it is.
It takes directly, so that's why we're not in the room.
So now we have posted a toy car for you too.
You who are under the bed ...
There were shivers when you came out.
Well?
Good!
You don't have to be afraid of something I said.
Do you want to play with us?
Play with this car that is under the bed and drives it out to us.
Play with it!
Play with that car.
That's it!
It is it ..
I said push the bus.
It tries to push the bus.
It was a voice before Tony, out here.
Well?
I belonged to it.
It lies and beats there.
It wants to push it away.
We won't go out of here ...
until you say your name.
It may be that PMB is running up there as well.
A bright light is captured by the surveillance in the room where the PMB stands.
Show yourself like a fog here.
Play the melody up in the other room.
If you are there by the closet.
I stand here thinking about a thing that feels pretty macabre ...
When we came here earlier today ..
So this door was closed.
No one in there.
What is also on this door is a hasp.
Huh?
At the top left.
I think you are a dark energy that has been generated in this place, of something very, very negative.
I even think you told this man, going out in the barn and hanging you.
Am I right there?
And so it increases.
It vibrates even more.
And you try to behave as if you are a small child.
So when the boy is to be able to talk to you ..
But we will tell those who live here, that the boy is talking to is no little girl.
So he'll stop talking to you.
It just lay down, the bus too.
Okay.
If you are going to do something big and strong, so do it now.
Because you are not the voice in this house any more.